commentarymagazine.com 2019-05-03

# Privacy Policy - Commentary

### Our Commitment to You

This site is owned and operated by _Commentary_. Visitors can get access to much of commentarymagazine.com (“this website”; “the website”; “ _Commentary_ “; “Commentary Online”) (be it via personal computers, mobile devices, or otherwise) without providing any personally identifiable information. But if you use this website to subscribe or buy products, you have entrusted to our care not only your reading time but your personal and financial data as well. At _Commentary_ , we want to make your online experience satisfying and safe. Commentary Online gathers certain types of information about users, and we feel that you should know how we use that information and understand that we hold ourselves to the highest standards in its safekeeping and use.

### The Information We Collect

We collect information in order to service your account, save you time, and better respond to your needs. When you register on the website, we ask you to create a user name and password. If you subscribe to the magazine through the website, we collect your name, address, country, phone number, and e-mail address. This information allows us to service your subscription efficiently. If you purchase products or services through our website, we also collect order information (for instance, a billing address) and credit-card numbers. Under no circumstances does _Commentary_ divulge an individual’s financial information or e-mail address to a third party.

We may collect certain technical and navigational information, such as computer browser type, Internet protocol address, pages visited, and time spent on our websites. This information may be used, for example, to alert you to software compatibility issues or to resolve technical or service problems, or it may be analyzed to improve our web design and functionality and our ability to serve you and your accounts.

We use “cookie” technology to collect site statistical information and improve your customer experience. However, we make very limited use of these data files. We do not use them to pull data from your hard drive, to learn your e-mail address, or to view data in cookies or other similar data files created by other websites. We will not share the information in these data files or give others access to it. Please note that you can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you have set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site.

### How We Protect Privacy Online

Our website uses some of the most secure forms of online communication available, including data encryption, Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol, and user names and passwords. These technologies provide a high level of security and privacy when you get access to your account information and initiate online transactions.

Within _Commentary_ , we restrict access to information about you to those employees who need to know the information in order to perform their jobs, such as servicing your accounts or notifying you of products and services. (Note that passwords are encrypted and that _Commentary_ cannot get access to them in any way. If you lose your password, you can reset it [here](https://www.commentarymagazine.com/my-account/).) To protect your personal information, we maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in keeping with industry standards and practices, and we review and adjust these safeguards regularly in response to advances in technology.

### Your Personal Information

Under no circumstances does _Commentary_ divulge an individual’s financial information or e-mail address to a third party. We may share other information with carefully selected vendors and business partners with whom we work. This includes companies that offer affinity programs and perform marketing services and other business operations. In certain instances, we may contract with companies to perform services for us. Where necessary, we will disclose information we have about you to these third parties. In all such cases, we provide the third party with only the information necessary to carry out its assigned responsibilities, and only for that purpose. And we require these third parties to treat your personal information with the same high degree of confidentiality that we do.

If you prefer that _Commentary_ not disclose personally identifiable information to vendors and partners who want to market products or services to you, please e-mail [service@commentarymagazine.com ](mailto:service@commentarymagazine.com)with “Opt-Out” in the subject line of the message.

Finally, we will release information about you if you direct us to do so, if we are compelled by law to do so, or in other legally limited circumstances (for example, to prevent fraud).

### Your E-mail Address

Under no circumstances does _Commentary_ divulge an individual’s e-mail address to a third party. We may use your e-mail address for the following types of e-mail messages:

  * A monthly reminder when a new issue of _Commentary_ is posted on the website.
  * Occasional updates about special articles and valuable offers.

You can also elect to receive other types of e-mail messages from us, including newsletters, alerts, or notifications. To do so, use this form below:

Please note that even if you opt-out of marketing e-mails, we will continue to send you e-mail service notifications that are related to your account. These include e-mails that provide account information, answer your questions about a product or service, and facilitate or confirm a sale.

### Keeping You Informed

We reserve the right to modify this policy at any time, but rest assured that if we do change it, we will promptly post the change(s) in this space.
